{
"question": "本",
"answer": "ほん"
},
{
"question": "迚も",
"answer": "とても"
},
{
"question": "会う",
"answer": "あう"
},
{
"question": "好き",
"answer": "すき"
},
{
"question": "分かる",
"answer": "わかる"
},
{
"question": "此れ",
"answer": "これ"
},
{
"question": "聞く",
"answer": "きく"
},
{
"question": "所",
"answer": "ところ"
},
{
"question": "先",
"answer": "さき"
},
{
"question": "何時も",
"answer": "いつも"
},
{
"question": "書く",
"answer": "かく"
},
{
"question": "沢山",
"answer": "たくさん"
},
{
"question": "入る-1",
"answer": "はいる"
},
{
"question": "置く",
"answer": "おく"
},
{
"question": "何処",
"answer": "どこ"
},
{
"question": "住む",
"answer": "すむ"
},
{
"question": "食べる",
"answer": "たべる"
},
{
"question": "歩く",
"answer": "あるく"
},
{
"question": "働く",
"answer": "はたらく"
},
{
"question": "着く",
"answer": "つく"
},
